https://www.dolphin-design.fr/company/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
MENUMENUSoC Expertise
SoC Expertise
Process nodes expertiseAdvanced low-power design techniquesUltra-low power SoC architectures
NEW PRODUCTSTSMC 22ULL CODEC
TSMC 22ULL Voice Activity DetectionContact us
Products
Semiconductor IP
IP CatalogPower Management IPAudio IPBody Bias IPFoundation IP
Platform Solutions
SPIDER – Power Management PlatformCHAMELEON – MCU SubsystemBAT – Analog & Digital audio platformSPEED Computing Platforms
NEW PRODUCTSTSMC 22ULL CODEC
TSMC 22ULL Voice Activity DetectionContact us
ASIC / SoC ServicesCustomer Support
Customer Support
Customer private spaceResource librarySupport requestEDA Solution download
LATEST NEWS
Discover a new and improved version of our Power Controller IP – MAESTRO – to speed-up energy-efficient SoC design
December 4, 2020
Our SPEED platforms receive the “Solar Impulse Efficient Solution” Label, rewarding profitable solutions that protect the environment.
October 16, 2020
Thalia and Dolphin Design announce partnership to transform analog IP re-use economics and to accelerate time to market
September 4, 2020
Search
Search
Close
CompanyBusiness ethicsCareersContact usEcosystemEventsManagement TeamNewsPolicies & EthicsPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy helps you understand the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our website https://www.dolphin-design.fr (the “Site”).We use your data to provide and improve the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.This privacy policy does not cover any other data collection or processing, including, without limitation, data collection practices of other websites to which we link or data that we or our affiliates collect offline or through web pages that do not display a direct link to this privacy policy.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personal information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage DataUsage DataWe may also collect information on how the Site is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Site and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amounts of data that may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyse our Site.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some parts of our Site.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataDolphin Design SAS uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the SiteTo notify you about changes to our SiteTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Site when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the SiteTo monitor the usage of the SiteTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTransfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside France and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to France and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Dolphin Design SAS will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataLegal RequirementsDolphin Design SAS may disclose your Personal Data only if such an action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Dolphin Design SASTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the SiteTo protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the publicTo protect against legal liabilityData RetentionThe time period for which Dolphin Design SAS retain your Personal Information depend on the purposes for which it is collected (see paragraph Use of Data). In any case this time period will not exceed 10 years.Security Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Site (“Service Providers”), to provide the Site on our behalf, to perform Site-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Site is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Site.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about your activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enLinks To Other SitesOur Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Right to Access and Change InformationYou have a right to access your personal information that we hold, in order to find out the information held and/or to correct it. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please write to us at:DOLPHIN DESIGN SAS, 1bisA Chemin du Pré Carré, 38240 MEYLAN – France.Tél. : + 33 (0)4 76 41 10 96.Or by e-mail: contact@dolphin.frPlease provide sufficient detail about the information in question to help us locate it.Right to Opting Out / Right to ErasureBy providing us with your Personal Information you consent to receiving Dolphin Design SAS related notices, messages or content, such as, but not limited to, Dolphin Design SAS News Alerts, third-party newsletters, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out or request deletion of your personal data by emailing us.Response delayWe commit to respond to your request for access, rectification or opposition or any other requests within a reasonable period of time, which may not exceed 1 month from the receipt of your request.Contact InformationThese Site is owned and operated by: DOLPHIN DESIGN SAS, 1bisA Chemin du Pré Carré, 38240 MEYLAN – France. Tél. : + 33 (0)4 76 41 10 96.If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:E-mail : contact@dolphin.fr
Platform Solutions
Semiconductor IP
ASIC / SoC Services
Customer Support
Company
Menu
Platform Solutions
Semiconductor IP
© 2019 Dolphin Design SAS – All Rights Reserved.
This site uses cookies. By continuing to use our website, you consent to our cookies. To learn more, please read our privacy policy.Ok
